{
    "subject": "resource/Mike_Simpson",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Idaho",
    "human_readable": "Mike Simpson was born in Idaho.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8752562403678894,
            "question": "Where was Mike Simpson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6802564263343811,
            "question": "Has Mike Simpson made any significant contributions to Idaho?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38868802785873413,
            "question": "What is Mike Simpson known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3056238293647766,
            "question": "Where does Mike Simpson currently reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22867929935455322,
            "question": "Is there anything else we know about Mike Simpson's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1990477591753006,
            "question": "Does Mike Simpson have any notable achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09885424375534058,
            "question": "What is Mike Simpson's stance on important social policies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09682819992303848,
            "question": "Who are some of Mike Simpson's influential colleagues or mentors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0942811444401741,
            "question": "What political positions has Mike Simpson held?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0875849798321724,
            "question": "What are Mike Simpson's views on current political issues?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mike Simpson was born in Idaho.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3342_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What political positions has Mike Simpson held?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3342_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of Mike Simpson's influential colleagues or mentors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3342_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Mike Simpson's stance on important social policies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3342_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3342_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3342_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3342_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3342_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3342_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3342_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3342_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3342_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3342_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3342_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Mike Simpson was born in Idaho\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that multiple documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3342/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3342/re-ranker-msmarco/16.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3342/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt, and others) confirm that Mike Simpson was born in Idaho, specifically in Burley."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Mike Simpson was an Idaho native, born in Burley, Idaho. Therefore, the statement \"Mike Simpson was born in Idaho\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}